I have no wishes anymore
Chaika - The Coffin Princess
My hope was hard as rock, and now it is brittle
My body is battered and broken,
and I will not last long
But I will look back on my proud life
with a mask of false courage
The reason flowers blossom
is to say goodbye and wither
This is the law of the world
All of mankind is cruel
We betray and we are betrayed
Goodnight, let us sleep now
You will hear a song
A sad, sad song
A song about you
Fill the blackness
Toru...
Toru! Toru, wake! Toru!
What is it?
Toru, look, look! Ahead!
What is that?
You don't know, Brother? That is called the ocean.
It's your first time seeing it, too, isn't it?
Toru, Akari, see ocean, first time?
The village of Acura was in the mountains.
My first time, too!
Feels cool...
Too salty!
Sideways walk.
Chaika!
It looks like big waves hit here sometimes, so be—
Toru, laugh! Mean!
Hey, stop that!
Brother might look rather good all wet.
I'll help you, Chaika.
You idiot! Cut it out!
I want to see that annoyed face more, as well.
You impress me, Brother.
You're the master of sopping wet love scenes!
Give it a res—
The Harbor of Phantom Dreams Recollected
This is the mansion of Clay Morgan, one of the eight heroes.
Yeah.
All we know about him is that he uses a spear.
I hope he's someone who can understand reason.
Chaika, what are you looking at?
Claudia's words... Father's fortune.
Hidden island.
Yeah, the rumor did say it was in the ocean around here...
Yes.
Hey, Chaika,
you know the battle for the remains is going to get tougher now, right?
The red Chaika already got one of them and is a step ahead of us.
Instead of talking about a fortune that we don't even know exists,
shouldn't we be trying to get more remains as quickly as we can?
Yes...
Sixty-four sheep...
What's going on?
Lots of people here, eh? And they're all uglier than me!
Why are all these people lined up here?
Clay Morgan loves to laugh, so he has many entertainers perform for him every day.
If we make him laugh, he gives us lots of money!
A hero who likes comedy? That's different.
In other words, we just have to look like entertainers.
That Gundo could be trouble.
Next!
Are you a ventriloquist?
Yep, that's right!
You're the third ventriloquist today.
We've seen enough. Go home!
Looks like the screening is fairly strict.
Yeah.
Next!
And you are?
We are a troupe of street performers.
Street performers, eh?
That's not unusual.
Is there anything unique you can do?
Yes! Ah...
Of course.
This man is a one-of-a-kind immortal.
He can sit naked in a tub of boiling water,
and impersonate a cockatrice while eating pasta through his nose.
That sounds amazing!
Okay, go on in!
Did you have to say all that?
It got us inside, didn't it?
Toru, pasta through nose, amazing!
Don't take it seriously!
I am Clay Morgan.
Are you the man who can sit naked in a tub of boiling water,
impersonating a cockatrice while eating pasta through your nose?
I'd love to see that. Show me.
Clay Morgan, I'd like to talk to y—
Strip, Brother.
What are you doing?
You need to be naked to sit in boiling water.
You just made all that up!
Why do I actually have to do it?
Because I want to see it.
Who cares?!
Do you hate me, Brother?
Are you the sort of man that would deny his sweet little sister's wish?
What's so sweet about forcing me to strip with a knife to my throat?!
Now that you've gotten my hopes up,
is it not your job as an older brother to live up to them?
You got your own hopes up!
Toru! Want to see, too!
You be quiet!
So you're a stand-up comedy troupe in the guise of street performers!
How novel! I like it!
Do come again sometime.
You may take your money and go.
Well, I guess that worked out...
We don't need the money.
We want the remains instead.
Emperor Gaz's remains.
Wh-Who are you people?!
The remains?!
I feel ill.
Leave!
Leave now!
Return Father's remains!
F-Father?
Gaz's daughter, Chaika!
You're...
That can't be! I saw... I saw you die!
Your head rolled!
It wasn't me! The one who killed you...
Hartgen was the one that killed you!
Why are you here?
Have you come to curse me?!
Stay away! Stay away, ghost!
Stay away!
He ran away...
What was that about?
Toru! Clay, where?!
He ran. We're going after him.
You wait in the vehicle.
I come with!
You can't run with your Gundo.
Leave this one to us.
Right...
Fredrica?
What are you guys doing here?
Good timing! Look after Chaika!
Huh?
Master Morgan?
He went running behind there like a madman not long ago.
He came in here earlier, and left through the back door.
Find him?
No. He seems to be running around with abandon.
Looks like he won't be returning to his mansion for a while.
Damn...
Fresh fish really is delicious!
Chaika, are you worried about the emperor's fortune?
Yes.
But nobody ever found that island, right?
Possible, entire island hidden, magic.
Oh, that's true.
Secret of Chaika... Information, desperate.
Ship...
Fredrica! Request, stay here!
Stay away, ghost servant!
Get away! Get away!
What are you so afraid of?
Are you that scared of the emperor you helped kill?
You weren't there! You didn't see what I saw!
He was stabbed, cut apart, covered with blood... but he was smiling!
As if he pitied us...
As if he were looking at ants...
He was no human. He was a monster!
You made me remember it all...
After I was finally enjoying life again!
You've been paying entertainers to make you forget about Emperor Gaz?
Where is she? Where is his daughter's ghost?
The rumor that his dead daughter was searching for his remains was true?!
Damn it! Disappear!
A secret island?
Never heard of it.
Rumor, clue, anything! Please!
I'm not sure what to tell you...
I don't know if it has any connection,
but there is a place off the coast that people call the Evil Sea.
Need details!
All boats that go near there end up sinking or going missing.
So none of the fishermen around here will go near it.
There's no island there, though.
Only ocean.
Evil Sea...
Have you lost your mind, starting a fight in here?
Shut up!
Stay away!
Keep her away from me!
Want to keep going?
If you want to kill me, go ahead!
I don't want to kill you.
All I want is the remains.
Just the remains?
Yes. Where are you hiding them?
If I give you the remains, will you go away?
Fine! You can have them!
Just leave me alone!
Any luck, Brother?
Yeah, it's here!
He was afraid to keep them anywhere near him,
so he hid them here?
Why didn't he just sell them?
There must be plenty of people who would want them.
He probably thought he'd be cursed if he got rid of them.
Okay, ready to head back?
You still love to show up out of nowhere, I see.
In the coastal waters northeast of here, there is an island.
That is where you should go next.
An island? Where Emperor Gaz's fortune is?
You'll find out when you get there.
Hold it!
Guy,
you knew that there were multiple Chaikas, didn't you?
And here's a question for you:
Do you really believe I'm the same Guy who spoke to you before?
You'll just keep jerking us around, won't you?
You are free to think what you will.
I still don't know how he does that.
Yeah. I'd guess it's some kind of magic, but...
He didn't say that what's on the island is more remains.
If gathering remains is our priority, we should probably follow Claudia's note.
Then we should head for the Principality of Hartgen?
Stephan Hartgen was the leader of the rebels.
If what Claudia and Clay said is true,
then he's the man who cut off Chaika's head.
Shin Acura, raise your head.
Yes, sir.
What is the status of the remains?
A large number of remains should soon arrive here in the Principality of Hartgen.
They will arrive with the one who currently possesses the most remains,
the white Chaika.
I see.
When all the remains are gathered, you're going to show me first, right, Father?
Hey, Arina, that's not fair.
You're going to show me, aren't you, Father?
Irina, Arina... My daughters.
Of course, I promise you two will be the first to see.
The white Chaika, eh?
I understand her two saboteurs are acquaintances of yours.
In a way.
Three people who grew up as family,
taking up arms to fight to the death...
I look forward to it.
I will have you do your job to the fullest, Shin.
Yes, sir.
And you, as well,
cavalier of lost honor.
Fredrica, where's Chaika?
Oh, she ran off earlier.
Where?!
Please, sail ship!
Reward, lots!
You've gotta be kidding! Anywhere but there!
Pay bonus!
Money's not worth dying at sea!
Please! Someone, help!
Chaika!
Toru...
What were you thinking?
It's not just Clay.
The red Chaika's group might be close by!
What if a fight had broken out?
Selfish actions, apologize.
But, serious.
Father's fortune, myself... Want to know.
That again?
Frankly, I'm against it.
We have no idea what this fortune is,
and what we do know is too vague.
Not to mention, if we know it's in such dangerous waters,
that's all the more reason to play it safe.
Your objective is to gather the remains, right?
We know where the remaining heroes are.
Why can't you get all the remains first,
and then think about the fortune?
New facts, one after another.
Many Chaikas. All created.
My memories, missing.
Everything, unclear.
Want to know everything.
But you don't know if you'll find anything out once you get his fortune...
Toru, can't understand my feelings!
Will search for fortune!
Even alone! Father's fortune!
Alone, you say?
In other words, you're firing us, then?
Saboteurs will risk their lives as tools to serve their master's purpose,
but once we're fired, that's it.
Later.
Toru...
What's done is done.
Akari...
Aww, they left.
You okay with that, Chaika?
Said I would work alone.
Can't stop Toru.
Yeah?
I wonder what I should do...
I only followed you guys because I wanted to fight Toru.
Fredrica, last favor! Just one!
Want to find island.
Dragoon, fly, Evil Sea!
Oh, you want me to take you close to the island?
Yes!
Sure, just going there is fine.
It sounds fun.
Grateful!
I guess we're camping here tonight.
We'll think tomorrow about what we should do starting tomorrow.
You never change, Brother.
Ever since we lived in Acura...
I understand that you want to keep Chaika out of danger.
What are you talking about?
I was only following the law of the saboteur.
Suppose you were to die, Brother.
And suppose the many lewd, repulsive things you owned were hidden on some island.
Where are you going with this?
If that were the fortune you had left behind,
I would go to find them, even to the ends of the world.
It's just the same as
the way Chaika values her father's remains as well as his fortune.
That being the case, shouldn't a saboteur respect his master's will?
You know how inept Chaika is.
This very night, she may be off somewhere being raped by some thug.
Or she may have fallen prey to some beast.
Or she may have encountered the red Chaika's gang,
and her head has left her body...
Okay, I get it!
I'll go back and talk to Chaika.
Good enough?
I'm just following your lead, Brother.
She's trying to get to the island alone?!
That idiot!
No way no how.
Any kind of boat will do! Just take us close!
Give it up.
No fisherman around here will take a boat out there.
What about that boat? Whose is it?
Oh, that's Master Morgan's cargo ship.
He runs the shipping industry around here, after all.
Wh-What? What do you want now?
We want to borrow your boat.
If you don't want Emperor Gaz's remains all over your house, that is...
Okay! I understand!
I'll take care of it now!
It's all so vague.
We're supposed to find an island no one's ever heard of?
What?
It's them!
This doesn't look like a coincidence.
Yeah. What should we do, Princess?
Efun... Heluste... Ru... Belguil... Fai... Sev...
Come, resounding perception.
The Locator!
Reaction... faint...
Fredrica! Ahead, right!
It's fogging up.
Hey! Get out here!
Well, well. Found us already?
I figured we'd run into you sometime.
You guys heard the same information we did, didn't you?
Whatever do you mean?
White girl, where?!
She had some things to do.
So, what do you want to do?
It could be fun to fight it out right here.
I don't want to sink to the bottom
of the ocean with you guys.
I especially don't want you putting
a hole in this boat with your magic!
That's up to you!
Ruler that controls...
Come, The Commander!
There! Found island!
Want to land?
Yes!
Dragoons?
They look like it, but I don't think they are.
What?!
Kraken?!
Damn monster!
I live on in you
I live inside you,
twisted and tainted
The ark of our genes
rocks on the water,
sailing for the end times
All that I can offer you
is the day our curse was broken,
but one day, one day,
we will meet again,
as long as you wait for me on this Earth
What is there to be lamented?
I think on the proof we lived together
and bite into my beautiful lips
I will devote my life, my love,
and whatever time I have left
to you
Father's fortune, on island?
Fredrica, moment before landing, crash!
Separated from her!
Here, where? Fortune, where?
Return safely, possible?
The Writhing Island
Next time: The Writhing Island.