What should I do?!
Takuto was trying to get rid of me...
...and go with Mitsuki to her audition.
I wouldn't let it happen.
After that...
...I kept them from getting to their destination...
...and did everything I could to accomplish my mission.
It went well.
By the time the two finally got there...
...the audition was over...
...and someone had already been chosen.
Well, then...
...I wonder what's going to happen today.
Huh?
When Watching TV, please do so in a well-lit
room and from a safe distance.
Do you understand?
Yes.
The Image Character for Mermaid Tear is...
...Wakamatsu Madoka-kun.
No way...
A
u
dition.
I completed my mission, right?
The Voice of Song that Can't Reach Him
Mermaid Tear Image Character
Audition Results Conference
I
Madoka-san!
Over here please!
Mitsuki!
Ooshige-san.
Hey!
Are you running away?!
Mitsuki!
You really...
I'm sorry, Ooshige-san.
I'm really sorry.
Why didn't you tell me you had throat cancer?
Eh?
Ah...
Wakaouji-sensei...
What?!
Anyways, Dr. Wakaouji...
...let's hurry up and take
Mitsuki-chan to the hospital.
Mitsuki-chan... do you mean Full Moon-san?
Of course I do!
This girl isn't the Mitsuki-chan that I know.
Eh?
Oh no... what should I do...
Who are you anyways?
What are you talking about?!
She's the one and only Mitsuki, of course!
Run for it!
What?
Mitsuki?
Wait right there!
Mitsuki!
Mitsuki?!
It seems like they didn't follow us...
What should I do?
They're going to realize that Full Moon  and the twelve-year-old me are the same person...
That's not going to happen!
To say you can transform...
A story that is way too far from reality!
I can't go back to those two now...
I can't be Full Moon  now...
Mitsuki...
Huh?
Here.
Don't just stare at the ground.
Let's get our of here.
They're a little big, so you'll have to make do.
Well...
Sometimes... I just want to leave this behind...
...and help that girl do what she wants...
It's sad, but...
...it'll be impossible to be Full Moon  now...
Hurry up, Dr. Wakaouji!
That girl couldn't have gotten very far yet!
Like I said...
I came to search for Mitsuki-chan, not that  girl.
That is  her!
I believed you on the phone, but...
...I hadn't seen her yet, so I guess this couldn't have been helped.
Anyways, I'm going to search for Mitsuki-chan by myself.
Ah.
Dr. Wakaouji!
Geez...
Then... I'll search by myself too!
You moron!
Man!
What are you spacing out for... that was dangerous!
Now's not the time for you to die yet!
You...
You...!
Hey.
Isn't that Full Moon ?
What?
She can't be.
There's no way she'd be in a place like this.
But...
What am I supposed to say at a time like this?!
Madam...
Some iced tea...
I'm fine.
But... aren't you tired from walking?
It's all right.
Why?
I see...
You haven't seen her?
Thanks.
Where are you, Mitsuki-chan?
Yes.
Our office is still refraining from commenting on Full Moon.
No.
How can you still say that?!
Yes.
Yes!
That's all, then...
Man...
How did this happen?!
I'm very sorry.
At this rate...
...we'll lose everything we had scheduled for tomorrow.
I understand!
I'll definitely find her before the day's over!
Hey, what's going on?
Hey! That's her manager's car!
Full Moon
Quit!?
As you can see...
...a car driven by someone related to Full Moon-san...
...has just rushed off from the office.
Full Moon
Quit!?
Just!!
Scramble!!
Takeda-san...
...you've met with Full Moon-san for your magazine before, right?
That's right.
She hadn't debuted yet, but...
...she's a very pure and good girl.
That kind of thinking is just naive.
Such pure feelings can't last in show business...
Maybe she just gave up and went home.
No.
She sings with true strength from the heart.
To think that it would end this way...
I don't want to believe it.
It looks like everything has fallen apart.
Eichi-kun...
My song probably...
...won't be able to reach you now...
Where am I?
Ah... I'm inside the lighthouse, huh?
Takuto... where'd he go off to?
Ah?
The moon pendant Eichi-kun gave me... it's ruined...
Even though I always... always treasured it...
Futari nitetta no kana
Was it the same for the both of us?
fuu
Ano toki kimi wo mamoru to kimeta no ni
Even though I decided to protect you back then...
A song?
Doushite omoide ni dekinaindarou
Why can't I seal you away in my memories...?
Toosugite chikasugite todokanai yo
You're too far away... too close to me... for me to reach...
That's my song...
Wasure yotte omoeba omou hodo
The more I try to forget...
Kimi ga ookiku natteku yo
The more you are in my thoughts...
What a soothing voice...
Who could it be?
Eh?
Eh?!
Takuto...
Nakinagara sagashitsuzuketa maigo no kodomo no you ni
Always in tears... I continue to search like a lost child...
Kedo soko ni wa eien nante aru wake nakute
But... a thing like eternity... doesn't really exist...
Dare mo shinjinakereba iinda yo tsubuyaita ne
"It's okay to not trust anyone"... you mumbled...
Futari nitetta no kana
Was it the same for the both of us?
Fuu
Ano toki kimi wo mamoru to kimeta no ni
Even though I decided to protect you back then...
Doushite omoide ni dekinaindarou
Why can't I seal you away in my memories...?
Toosugite chikasugite todokanai yo
You're too far away... too close to me... for me to reach...
Wasure yotte omoeba omou hodo
The more I try to forget...
Kimi ga ookiku natteku yo
The more you are in my thoughts...
La la la la la la la
It sounds so... painful...
La la la la
I see...
I'm the only one who can hear Takuto singing...
La la la la la
La la la la la la la
That's right.
It's not just my song...
All those people...
Even Takuto...
Besides...
Surely, someday... Eichi-kun will...
I...
...really want to sing!
What are you doing?
Eh?
Well... you see...
Back in the old days, people used to get up early to catch salmon...
What are you talking about?
So...
...what are you going to do now?
What should I do...
Get on a boat...
...and sail off to America, huh?
What?
If you try to sing in America...
...you'll get Eichi's attention faster, right?
America, huh?
Let's do it.
Ah?
Give up here and go to America...
It might be better there.
Mitsuki...
Ah, but...
Will we be all right?
W-What do you mean?
My English.
Huh?!
'Cause... "Love Me Do" is read Ra-bu Me Do.
You're finally back to normal.
You're best with a smile on your face.
Takuto...
It's beautiful...
Yeah.
Takuto...
I...
Wakaouji-sensei...
...and Ooshige-san...
I think I should tell them everything.
Huh?
After I tell them everything...
...it can't be helped if they don't forgive me.
I... still want to sing.
But, Takuto...
You won't be a Shinigami anymore...
Are you okay with that?
As long as you're doing what you want to...
...I'll keep on following your dream.
Thank you, Takuto!
S-Stupid... don't just hug me for no reason at all!
I like your singing, Takuto.
So you did hear me...
That's 'cause...
...you're a gentle person...
Someone I can talk to...
You're trying to embarrass me again!
That's 'cause... it's the truth!
Saying "Like..."
Don't say that so easily... stupid Mitsuki...
Not when the one you like the most... is that Eichi...
Reception Room
Mitsuki-chan!
Wakaouji-sensei... Ooshige-san...
I'm sorry for causing you so much trouble!
Eh?
Mitsuki-chan... is your fever gone?
What about your cough?
I'm fine.
Anyways... let's go to the hospital.
I'll call your grandma immediately.
No.
Wakaouji-sensei.
I have something I need to tell you.
What?
You need to tell us something?
Aren't you Mitsuki-chan's little sister, Mikazuki-chan?
That's what you told me when we last met.
Sorry...
Back then... I was lying.
What?
Ooshige-san...
I'm Mitsuki.
Th-Then...
Who's the Full Moon  I'm always with?
That's also me.
There's no way that could be true...
That's what I came to talk to you about.
Mitsuki!
Be strong.
Okay.
Wakaouji-sensei...
Do you remember the day I asked you about the audition?
Yeah...
In reality...
After you left...
...something happened...
...right before my eyes...
A Shinigami by the name of Takuto appeared.
He told me that I had just one year left to live...
A Shinigami... and that you have only one year left to live...
That kind of story is...
Ooshige-san.
Let's listen to her story a little longer.
Okay...
Please go on.
Okay.
After I heard that...
I thought that this would be my only chance to audition and become a singer.
But... twelve-year-olds couldn't audition...
So then... Takuto...
I get it.
This will turn you into a sixteen-year-old.
Ever since then...
...I've been able to turn my body into that of the sixteen-year-old Full Moon.
I'm the only one who can see Takuto, so...
...I know that it's hard for you to just believe what I'm saying...
But if you don't believe me...
...I'll never be able to sing as Full Moon  again!
I understand what you're saying, but...
...can that all be real?
Oh well.
If they won't believe your story...
...we'll just have to show them.
Takuto!
Okay?
Yeah.
Wakaouji-sensei... Ooshige-san...
My story wasn't a lie.
Please watch closely.
Takuto...
I'm counting on you.
Okay.
Wakaouji-sensei... Ooshige-san...
This is me as a sixteen-year-old.
Mitsuki...
Do you believe what I say now?
H-Hey... Mitsuki...
Is this real?
This must be some kind of optical illusion or something, right?
It happened right before your eyes and you still don't believe her!
Ah!
What is this?!
That's Takuto.
I'm the Shinigami, Takuto.
This isn't how I usually look...
...but I can only talk to you when I'm in this form.
A-Are you really a Shinigami?
We have no choice but to believe it.
Thanks to Takuto-kun's power...
...Mitsuki-chan can change into a sixteen-year-old...
After learning that...
...everything that's happened since then...
...it all makes sense now.
But...
...to say that Mitsuki-chan only has one year left...
That's the only thing that I can't accept.
Despite that...
We can't allow her to use her throat constantly...
But when she's a sixteen year old...
...she's totally healthy.
What?
Is that true?
Yep.
No way... how can that be...?
If you don't believe it, run a test on her later.
So, Sensei... I want to keep on singing.
I beg you!
I can't let you, Mitsuki-chan...
Why?!
I'm running out of time.
In the time that I have left...
...I want to keep on singing!
I can't waste a second... I want to tell Eichi-kun how I feel!
And then...
That's not it.
Eh?
It's not about singing and living.
You sing to live...
You live to sing...
Ooshige-san...
Dr. Wakaouji.
Can't we do something about Mitsuki?
Until Mitsuki's dream comes true...
Just until then...
I'm begging you, Wakaouji-sensei!
Mitsuki-chan...
...can you give me some time?
I want to think this over.
I'd like to do as much as I can for you.
It's your life we are talking about here.
Doushite doushite suki nandarou
Why... just why have I fallen in love with you...
I want to help your dreams come true.
Konna ni namida afureteru
Yet, still... I can't stop my tears from falling...
Dr. Wakaouji seems like a wonderful person.
Cheer up Mitsuki!
I lost way too much back then
Ano koro wa ushinau mono ga oosugite
Nani mo utaenakatta
I couldn't sing at all
Sukoshi hanareta basho
That place you had to leave for a while...
Soko ga watashi no ibasho datta
It happened to be the place where I was
On that day I could see...
Kimi no hitomi no oku ni ano hi
Samishisa wo mitsuketa
The desolation lying in your eyes
I wonder if it's the same for both of us?
Futari niteru no kana
fuu
Kizukeba itsumo tonari ni itekureta
If you would just notice, I'm always by your side
Doushite konna ni suki nandarou
Why do I love you so?
Kimi no koe kanashii hodo hibiiteru yo
Your voice is calling out with such sadness
Ima made nani ga sasaedatta ka
I never knew what was supporting me, back then, and even now
Until we became so far apart...
Tooku hanarete wakatta yo
Preview
Hey, Takuto.
Is this okay?
Meroko's going to leave.
What... you're not mad at her?
It's her fault that you didn't make it to the audition.
That's true, but...
...Meroko must have had her reasons.
Man... how long are you going to keep on trusting people?
It's none of my business now.
If she wants to come back, she can come back on her own.
Geez, Takuto!
Next time on Full Moon wo Sagashite:
Meroko, Left Alone
Look forward to it!