No one's home.
I'm here, but I'm not here.
Leave already!
Let's see...
Oh, dang it!
What a big box!
2/13 GUARANTEED-DELIVERY MERCHANDISE
Valentine's Day Gift
Oh, this!
Whoa...
I'm home!
Sasami! Your Big Brother is home!
Would you like to eat first or have a bath?
Or do you want ME?
Food.
Sure. I've got some nice Spanish mackerel today.
And?
And for dessert, we've got some jelly and...
Pudding.
Oh, you knew I got some pudding, too?
That's my Sasami.
You know everything about me.
That is indeed the proof of love.
There, enjoy your food!
Feed me.
You're such a baby.
I'll starve to death.
I guess I have no choice then.
Say "ah!"
Big Brother.
What is it, Sasami?
Wash me.
You're such a baby.
Sasami, don't you think it's about time
for you to go to school?
I can't.
You're only 16 years old. You're young,
with your whole life ahead of you.
The future before you is infinite.
There's nothing in this world that you can't do.
I can't.
You finally made it to high school.
Why don't you enjoy school life a little?
I can't!
My mindless and boring job as a teacher
could be so much more enjoyable if you came.
Stop whining.
Dry me.
Yes, Sasami.
Dress me.
Brush.
Yes, Sasami.
You're not asleep yet? Staying up late
is bad for your skin.
Shut up.
Oh, let me know if you need anything. See you tomorrow.
It's time for late-night anime.
At the fingertip of God
My seasons are made
It's much longer than the starry sky
The song shakes up the sleep
Sasami-san
@Ganbaranai
It felt like my existence got wiped out
When I stood in the crowd covering my ears
To play what's in my heart
I'm not that mature to be able to select the noise
The flower that I found in the wilderness
It's scary yet gentle
The moment I touch it
Even the diorama could turn into reality
God drew the map for my future as a joke
Because the thousands of melodies echo
I destroy the tomorrow that's chasing me
The bond that cuddles under the starry sky
I saw the warmth
The bond that's born from the pain
That's the kind of bond I want to protect
Sasami-san @
Ganbaranai
Episode 1
"I'll Do My Best... Starting Tomorrow"
ALL ROADS
CLOSED
DETOUR
ROAD
CLOSED
Say "Ahhhn".
Ahhhn.
I'm going to school now.
Come to school if you change your mind.
Big Brother.
Here's your bento.
You packed a bento for me?
Oh, what a wonderful day it is today!
Let's make it a Sasami Day today!
Oh, now that I think about it, today is February 14th.
SASAMI LICKY-LICK ANNIVERSARY
SASAMI SUPER-SOFT ANNIVERSARY
SASAMI EYE-CONTACT ANNIVERSARY
SASAMI... SO CUTE...SO CUTE...
SASAMI CREAM-PUFF ANNIVERSARY
SASAMI BEAUTIFUL SUMMER
SASAMI CHOMP CHOMP ANNIVERSARY
SASAMI SASAMI-SAAAAAAAAN
SASAMI WOBBLE ANNIVERSARY
SASAMI PUNI-PUNI ANNIVERSARY
SASAMI HOKKORI ANNIVERSARY
SASAMI MELLOW ANNIVERSARY
SASAMI SUZUKI ANNIVERSARY
Both "Sasami Head-Over-Heel Anniversary"
SASAMI
HEAD-OVER-HEEL ANNIVERSARY
and "Sasami's-So-Much-in-Love-with-Big-Brother
Dynamites Anniversary" are today!
SO-MUCH-IN-LOVE-WITH-BIG-BROTHER
DYNAMITES ANNIVERSARY
But it's okay.
We're going to add "Sasami's Bento Anniversary" to that
and let's have a big party!
No!
That's for lunch, so don't open it until lunchtime.
Okay, if you say so...
Well, see you later then.
See you later!
Big Brother Surveillance Tool...
Activate!
Big Brother
Surveillance System
I'm leaving now!
It's just as if Sasami and I are a married couple!
Tsukuyomi    Kamiomi
Sasami
Ugh...
Whatever. Just go to school.
Oh?
Ribbit! Ribbit!
Tama is a cute and energetic froggy!
Tama!
Papa-lin, good morning!
What are you doing? You'll catch a cold.
I can't find the froggy.
That's why I'm doing the froggy instead. Ribbit, ribbit!
Froggy is hibernating right now.
Hibernating?
What would you do if someone was making a lot
of noise while you were trying to sleep?
I'd kill them!
See? That's why you should let him sleep for now.
Just play with him again when spring comes.
Okay! Tama is not going to disturb his sleep!
Hey, Tama is hungry!
Oh? That can't be helped. Why don't I give this to you?
This is supposed to be my lunch,
but I'll buy something at the cafeteria.
You're an idiot, Big Brother!
I won't let him get away with it today!
Not again...
This is...
No...
Big Brother...
I just... can't do it...
RIBBIT
Note: The Japanese onomatopaoeia "Kero," for Ribbit Ribbit Ribbit
sounds like "Gero," the onomatopoeia for throwing up
I VOMITED
I just... can't do it.
Big Brother, you idiot.
That was the first chocolate that I'd given to anyone.
YOU CAN BE MY FIRST.
Miss Tsurugi, I don't think you should be
playing eroge in the faculty room.
Note: Eroge is a contraction of the Japanese for "Erotic Game"
Miss Tsurugi,
I don't think you should
be playing eroge
in the faculty room.
SHUT UP AND DIE
Give my tea back.
Oh yeah, Tsukuyomi, did you get any chocolate?
No, not really.
Oh yeah? Then here.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I did it only because I feel sorry for how pathetic you are.
What?
Don't you get it?
The first person who's given you
Valentine's Day chocolate is me!
I'm supposed to be the first one!
How dare she?
You old loli wench!
Oh...
RIBBIT
I VOMITED
Whatever...
My life sucks.
It's totally not even worth trying.
Note: Kamiomi is dancing the Hare Hare Yukai,
of The Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya fame
You're creeping me out.
But I have nothing better to do, Kagami.
Why don't we chat?
You pick the topic you want to talk about.
"Today's Sasami" or "Yesterday's Sasami"
or "Sasami's Charms"
or "The Day I Had An Argument With Sasami"
or the ultimate topic...
"Sasami's Embarrassing Moments"!
Let's talk about Sasami, the most
interesting topic in the world,
until we run out of stuff to talk about!
Oh?
I was sleeping.
Big Sis Kagami!
What's going on?
What's this? Tama!
Papa-lin?!
Umm, I do like you a lot, too, but I want to start
the relationship as friends first.
What am I supposed to do?
You're going to kill me.
We've got all three sisters here.
Hey, Sis.
Big Sis Tsurugi!
I don't know what you guys are talking about,
but don't count me out.
Big Sis Tsurugi, listen. Guess what?
Papa-lin proposed to me!
What?
That chocolate must've given her the wrong idea.
Valentine's Day?
To put it simply, it's the day you give
chocolate to someone you love.
Is that right? Oh, no... That's a lie! It's impossible!
Unlike me, Sasami has common sense,
so I was certain she knew about Valentine's Day
and that she was in love with me!
But I still haven't received any chocolate from her!
Oh, I get it!
I bet she's going to give it to me,
saying "I love you, Big Brother"
in her maid outfit or something at dinner!
I'm not!
There's no time to waste!
I must go get lots of chocolate right now.
Thank goodness. He just didn't know
about Valentine's Day.
Oh, well, if that's the case
I should get chocolate for him again.
For your beloved Big Brother
Valentine's Day Chocolate
Other customers also bought... We recommend...
Oh? I didn't know this manga had a new issue.
DESCRIPTION
SYNOPSIS
Takuya tries to become the top chocolatier.
Let's see... This chapter's synopsis.
"The two fail to be honest with themselves
and end up arguing with each other.
But Kakao reflects on his action
after seeing Chiyoko's tears
and decides to become the best chocolatier!"
DESCRIPTION
THIS CHAPTER'S SYNOPSIS
Takuya tries to become the top chocolatier.
Chocolate is everything.
Chocolate is great!
"...Chocolate is everything. Chocolate is great!
I don't care about Chiyoko anymore!
A shocking new development!!"
I don't care about Chiyoko anymore!"
A shocking new development!!
That's too much of a new development!
Isn't this "Angels' Love"?
Choco Manga Monument
Angels' Chocolate
"Angels' Chocolate"...
Where did the chocolate come from anyway?
Oh?
Choco, Choco and Chocolate
(Special Limited Edition)
Note: Parody of Love, Elections and Chocolate
Choco, Choco and Chocolate
Blu-ray now on sale,
"Choco, Choco and Chocolate"?
(Special Limited Edition)
Choco, Choco and Chocolate
This one is only chocolate?
What happened to the love and the election?
DESCRIPTION
School cultural festival is right around the corner.
Chocolate between the two prompts further progress!
"The school cultural festival is right around the corner.
Chocolate between the two prompts further progress"...?
"Sword, magic and chocolate Battle Action"...
DESCRIPTION
Sword, magic and chocolate
battle action!
"This story contains explicit visuals and chocolate."
DESCRIPTION
This story contains explicit visuals
and chocolate.
DESCRIPTION
Choco-choco the chocolate,
which was stolen by chocolate.
It's the chocolate and heartrending chocolate story.
The two chocolate each other and become chocolate.
"Choco-choco the chocolate
which was stolen by Chocolate.
It's the chocolate and heartrending chocolate story.
The two chocolate each other and become chocolate"?
I don't even understand what that means anymore...
Oh yeah!
That has to be a Valentine's Day joke.
If I check out other sites...
"Secretary of Chocolate declares chocolate"...
Secretary Of Chocolate Declares Chocolate
SECRETARY OF CHOCOLATE
"I was told I wouldn't have a successful career
if I didn't attend the chocolate meeting".
[I was] Told I Wouldn't Have A Successful Career
If I Didn't Attend The Chocolate Meeting
CHOCOLATE MEETING
"...Regarding the issues of Chocoslovakia"...
Regarding the issues of Chocoslovakia
CHOCOSLOVAKIA
"Today's weather is chocolate
with occasional white chocolate.
Today's weather is chocolate
Some areas will have macadamia nuts chocolate
Some areas will have macadamia nuts chocolate."
OCCASIONAL WHITE CHOCOLATE
What is this? Don't tell me...
I didn't realize there were so many different
kinds of chocolate these days.
I'm going to buy tons of chocolate and give it to Sasami.
"There's no way I can eat this much chocolate,
so I'll give you some, Big Brother.
"D-don't get the wrong idea though.
"I just don't want to end up gaining weight
by eating too much of it."
She'll give me a very tsundere reaction
by saying stuff like that!
In that case, I'd be able to receive chocolate
from her in a legitimate manner.
Oh no... It's corrupted...
It's just like "Hansel and Gretel".
Tama, you can eat all you want today.
Really?
Come on! I'll teach you a lesson!
Thank you for the food!
It's delicious!
It's sweet.
Since it's chocolate.
I'm licking it.
Eat it!
Since it's chocolate!
You moron!
THIS is where you were supposed to
shoot the boobie missiles!
What?
Don't give up just because they're small!
Mind your own business!
Choco-choco-chocolate!
Note: Kagami is riffing Chise from Saishuu Heiki Kanojo (Saikano)
All right. The target is:
Tsukuyomi's house!
You're nothing, you evil god!
Kagami, show the world!
O human world... be restored to the way it should be.
I'm home.
Sasami, your Big Brother is home!
Today is supposedly called Valentine's Day!
They say today is the day women give men chocolate,
but since my love for you transcends age,
gender or blood relations, it doesn't really matter!
S-Sasami!
I see! Basically this means, "eat me". Correct?
If that's the case I'm not going to hold back.
I'll lick and bite.
Your big brother will...
Don't...
Don't give...
Don't give me...
Don't give me that...
Don't give me that crap!
Die!
We couldn't help it.
Get out of here!
This is MY house!
Sasami-san @ Ganbaranai
I'm beat...
I'll never work hard at anything.
You say so but that's not how it's going to be, Sasami.
In case you didn't know, you're supposed
to sing the ending song after every episode,
so grab your mic and sing! Sing it loud!
Whose idea is this anyway? This is bullshit. I'll kill them.
Sasami!
You're revealing your true feelings!
You have to act more innocent! You can do it. Come on!
You're asking too much!
But can't you hear the pre-recorded song
playing in the background?
Isn't that good enough?
Do I really need to sing it every single time? I don't, right?
Don't be like that!
Sharing your lovely voice with all the viewers
out there is as precious as this Earth!
Hey, Sasami! Are you listening to me?
Why are you hiding in the futon?
You can't tell me that you won't do it!
Give it your best! Efforts won't betray you!
Oh boy... In the end, she never came out of the futon.
But I promise you that you'll hear
Sasami's lovely voice next time!
So look forward to it!
Sasami-san@Ganbaranai
It's time for "Ganbaranai Fortunetelling".
Ganbaranai
Fortunetelling
This week's love reading for Capricorns.
LOVE THIS WEEK                    Ganbaranai Fortunetelling
Capricorn with a Good Life
If you're a Capricorn with a good life,
you are on the ball! Treasure the time with your lover.
Water-blue colored items may bring you good fortune.
LOVE THIS WEEK                    Ganbaranai Fortunetelling
Capricorn with a
Not-So-Good Life
If you're a Capricorn with not-so-good life,
things are just so-so. Good things may happen
while you're living... That's just a guess.
Don't worry about it. Wipe your tears away.
Next time, Episode 2:
"Security Personnel at Home"
Episode 2
"Security Personnel
at Home"