You're all right?
Guren!
Hey, Yuu.
Glad to see you're doing well.
Seraph
of the End
I knew you humans couldn't be trusted.
Stand aside, vampire!
What the hell's going on?
This man...
Oh? What happened to all that strength you had back in Shinjuku?
He's a completely different person!
Guren!
It's time.
Feast on human, demon, and progenitor blood.
Hey, Guren!
The hell's wrong with you?!
What are you doing?!
Seraph of the End.
It's coming, Aoi!
Divine retribution upon those
who dared to play with the forbidden.
Control that energy!
What is that?
A...
An angel...
Mirai!
Sickening humans, your time has come.
Breathtaking, isn't it?
Restrain the angel!
Y-You...
What the fuck do you think you're doing
to my little sister?!
Calm down, kid.
Wh...
What are you doing?!
Now, Yuu!
What's wrong, you big softie?
Do it.
You're kidding, right?
Tell me none of this shit is real!
You wouldn't betray your comrades, right?
Damn it, say something, Guren!
Aren't we...
Aren't we your family?!
Guren...
Yuu!
Yuu?!
Mirai!
It's here.
Summoned forth by the fifth trumpet, the angel of the abyss...
Abaddon.
Humanity has finally succeeded in harnessing the Seraph of the End.
Very good. Let it have the rest.
Sir.
We need to escape!
Let's go, Kimizuki!
No way in hell!
I can't leave my sister behind!
Wait, Kimizuki!
You guys leave without me!
I have to do this on my own.
Kimizuki!
Mika...
It's all over.
This nightmare ends now!
Move!
G-Guren...
Yuu...
Good.
Everything's going to be okay.
We'll go someplace safe—
Where's Guren?
He was crying...
I need to help him.
You need to let that go.
Where are Shinoa and the others?
The girl and her squad stayed back.
Then we gotta go save them!
They're my family.
I'm your only family!
You're wrong!
Guren, Shinoa, Yoichi,
Kimizuki, Mitsuba, and you...
You're all part of my family!
Mika...
Mika!
Hurry, drink my blood!
I-It won't help.
I can't recover within this field.
Then what can I do?!
There's nothing you can do.
That monster is unstoppable.
If you go now, you'll still make it.
Help them.
Shut up!
There's no way I'm leaving you behind!
I've only...
I've only just gotten you back!
I can't leave you again!
Just go, you idiot.
You'll lose your family again.
I just need to kill that monster, right?
That'll save everyone.
Stubborn as always, huh?
I told you, it's impossible.
I'm not the same as I was then.
Yuu?
You're that desperate?
Yup.
My power alone won't be enough, you know.
I know.
So you'll just betray me
for that trumpet, is that it?
You traitor.
Sorry about that.
That's the worst possible call.
You won't have a single shred
of humanity left after using that.
That's okay.
Anything to protect my family.
K-Krul...
This won't be good.
It stopped attacking.
What's going on?
It's probably because of that.
Well, what else?
Yuu!
Yuu?
Please, Yuu...
Save my sister...
What is that?
Lieutenant General Kureto, we're picking up an unknown Seraph of the End presence.
It's originating from that pillar of fire.
And that means what, exactly?
I'm unsure.
However, if we do not act on it...
...the world shall end once more.
Divine retribution, huh?
Though the heavens may move against us,
humanity shall keep marching forward!
Aoi!
Sir.
Annihilate it.
Understood.
All units, move out!
The target is the Seraph of the End!
Forward, angel!
This is the end.
Those who have broken the taboo shall crumble as pillars of salt!
Shit!
Get out of its way!
We don't have time!
Attack!
That's the second trumpet!
Lieutenant General Kureto,
it's the King of Salt!
I don't care!
Kill him!
Shit!
Yuu.
Yuu...
This is the end.
Today, the endless lust and greed of humanity will be as salt cast away by the wind!
All units!
Capture Hyakuya Yuuichirou and restrain him!
Sir!
Hey, Yuu.
Teetering off the deep end too, aren't you?
Sickening humans.
I'm glad, Yuu.
You came for my help in the end.
Unfortunately,
in order to keep that thing under control,
I really have no other choice but to do this.
This looks bad.
We have to go!
We should get moving too, Krul.
Can you move?
I'm fine.
Good.
Don't let the humans get their hands on Yuu.
We'll retrieve him ourselves.
Yeah.
I'm not done yet!
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Too hasty, my queen.
Your beautiful neck is wide open.
Y-You!
Krul!
Stay back!
Curse you...
Go!
Good morning.
Wow, Ferid.
You really did take her down.
Praise me some more.
Whatever.
I think it's about time I ask you
what your goals are.
Fellow vampires!
Krul Tepes has been found
guilty of serious treason!
That is, her involvement in the
Seraph of the End experiments.
Therefore, I, Seventh Progenitor Ferid Bathory, will henceforth assume command.
Kill those humans!
Hey, you're alive.
Glad you could make it...
Narumi.
I don't have time.
Hurry up and give him—
I'm sorry, Lieutenant Colonel.
I can't follow your orders right now.
Narumi!
Hurry!
Move.
Don't let them get away!
Lieutenant General Kureto.
They're coming!
Damn vampires.
Kill them all!
Explain, Guren.
I said I wanted an explanation!
Don't fucking laugh!
Don't be so mad, Shinya.
This is what we dreamt about
when we were kids.
The hell are you talking about?
I'm changing the world.
I'm bringing about a world where foster sons like you and branch family members like me can rise to the top.
What the fuck are you saying?!
Good men of ours have died!
Because of your betrayal,
all of our friends—
Don't...
Don't tell me you've been possessed by...
Hey, Guren!
Can you hear my—
Shinoa!
Kimizuki's sister is still...
It's fine for now.
Kimizuki...
Hand over Hyakuya Yuuichirou!
This is an order!
As of now, the Hiiragi Shinoa squad
will withdraw from the Demon Army!
Stay sharp!
Let's move!
Let's go, everyone!
We will come out of this alive!
Four months later
Lieutenant General Kureto.
We're ready to advance.
All right.
It's showtime.
Looks like things are just about
to get more interesting.
Is this it?
Yes!
Where are they?
They should be here any minute.
You're late!
You guys are just too early.
Yuu, how's your demon doing?
Hm?
Oh, it's fine.
Just taking a little nap.
Now, let's go!
We're gonna save Kimizuki's li'l sis,
and that dumbass Guren too while we're at it!
Is the lieutenant colonel really in Sanguinem?
Yes, it's solid information.
Jeez, we ran away from there
only to come all the way back?
Let's hope your brain doesn't
go back to how it was too.
What was that, Mika?!
What the hell's that supposed to mean?
It means you'll become even more stupid.
Ouch. That's harsh.
He'll be fine.
He's as stupid as it gets.
You hear that, Yuu?
What a relief.
Yuu?
It's starting to rain.
War in Nagoya
At first light, the moon is brought low
reimei ni tsuki wa korogeochite
by a far greater power
shitataka na kirameki ni kakusareru
Our love is manifest,
kanjou ni kanketsu suru omoi
but our hearts are lacking
dare no kokoro mo tsumugenai
A distant prayer
yuuen no inori
The order we believed in is a lie
shinjiteita chitsujo ga uso naraba
What have we left but to sacrifice our hearts
jibun no kokoro de sura junshoku shite
on the fiery altar of service?
kuruitateru honoo matou
The little we create is ruined soon after
umidashite wa hakai suru hakoniwa
Our swords bite into the hand that wields them,
tatoe nigiru tsurugi ga moroha demo
but you still have to resist
subete ushinau made
until all is lost
aragae trickster
The
End
Illustrated by Satoshi Kadowaki