Huh?
Rin.
Stop it!
Look at you, ganging up and
bullying her this way!
You're just a couple of slimeballs!
Absolute slimeballs!
Back off, Tohsaka. This is none
of your business!
Fine.
Then why not treat me
the same way?
Then it'll be my business, too.
Come on.
Forget this!
Here.
Japanese
Year 2
You used too much mana at once.
Keep your mind on the task.
In order to control mana,
you must maintain control of your mind.
If you lose control,
all the mana will rebound on you.
Use too much, and you risk
not only yourself,
but those around you.
Always endeavor to maintain
the proper flow.
That's the essence of the
Tohsaka family creed.
Act with composure and elegance.
You have to stick up for
yourself, Kotone.
When they act like that,
you have to get mad!
You're so cool, Rin-chan.
I could never tell them off that way.
I'm not cool.
It's perfectly normal and natural.
Yeah... Natural.
Hold out your hand.
Teach me more, Father!
How can I make something like this?
I don't know...
Right now, it might be a
little difficult for you.
But if you practice every day,
you'll be able to do it, too.
Remember, you're a daughter
of the Tohsaka family.
Hey, Rin-chan,
could you please help me
with a problem?
Sure, which one?
Me, too!
And me!
They teach you the method
on page twenty-three.
You just have a small math error here.
Oh!
This problem...
See? It's just like this example.
Wow...
Rin-chan, you're great!
Kotone?
Sit down. I'll walk you through it.
Okay!
Do we really have to live
with the Zenjo?
Once the Holy Grail War begins,
Fuyuki City will no longer be safe.
But I want to help you win
the Holy Grail War...
Rin, don't upset your father.
Are we in the way?
Not at all.
I just want to make doubly sure that
everything goes exactly
according to plan.
And part of that is ensuring you
and your mother are safe.
You'll be much safer outside Fuyuki City.
There's gotta be some way I can help!
Yeah, I just haven't learned everything
I need to know yet.
All I have to do is study on my own!
I-I don't understand a word of this...
What the heck?
Jeez!
Du, wer die Tur geoffnet hat, wird Freunde sein.
Gotta close it.
Fur die Aussage nimm meine Hand.
Wir weden in meinem Zimmer treffen.
Sind deine Hande, Klein? Gross?
It won't move!
Schlank? Steif?
Rin, are you all right?
Jede Hand ist dankbar.
Ich will sie erhalten.
Ich schneide sie vorsichtig...
It's still too early for you
to read that book.
You'll encounter things in this world
that are, themselves,
imbued with mana.
This is called a mana compass.
Normally, it won't point
toward anything.
But when you get near
traces of mana...
Rin, put some mana into this.
Okay.
It reacts like so.
Now take that book...
That reaction means it's something
beyond your ability,
so you should be careful.
You may have this. Consider it
an early birthday present.
Thank you, Father!
When the Grail War is over,
I'll give you a real education
in Gem Magic.
Not long after, strange things
started happening.
Another study hall?
Study Hall
Another kidnapping was on
the news this morning.
Kidnappings continue
In Fuyuki City, cases of children suddenly
disappearing are becoming frequent.
The teachers have been meeting all day.
Meeting in progress
There's not gonna be a fifth period today!
Fifth period canceled
Beware suspicious individuals
when walking to
and from school!!
All right!
But we have to go home...
How come?
Kidnapping...
But it's only children being kidnapped.
Hey, did you hear?
The corpse isn't in the casket.
Its condition must have
been too gruesome.
It happened in Fuyuki, right?
H-Hi, I'm Tohsaka,
one of Kotone-chan's classmates...
Sorry, we're not home right now.
Please leave your message
after the beep.
Please be okay...
Kotone.
So this is Fuyuki after dark...
It's totally different...
I don't like this feeling.
What's happening?
I've never seen it do this.
Does it mean traces of mana
are everywhere?
I have to find Kotone!
Going for a walk with your kid this late?
What was that?
Uh-oh!
That was close. If they'd seen me,
they'd have taken me home.
Come on... Pick up your feet.
Two of them?
There's another kid now.
But why?
This is pointless...
Why am I hiding?
I can't do anything like this!
No one's here?
H-Hey!
Kotone?
Kotone! Kotone!
Someone's done something to her.
What do I do? I have to help...
Oh? What's wrong? Are you lost?
No... I...
It's perfect.
We're just about to start the party.
But we need more people.
Won't you help?
You know, like they say,
the more, the merrier.
No!
What was that?
Don't try to run...
He's using that bracelet on them?
Ow!
I have to break it!
Ah, so you're going to help, after all!
Huh?
What's that?
You used too much mana at once.
I'll destroy this thing!
What...
Kotone!
Rin-chan...
What is this place?
There's no time to cry!
Everyone, run!
Wait! Stop!
He's probably gonna be pissed.
Huh?
Where's Rin-chan?
Thank goodness...
Time to go home.
I did it, Father.
Huh?
That reaction means it's something
beyond your ability,
so you should be careful.
Rin...
I can't believe she went to Fuyuki...
Rin!
Rin...
Rin-chan's fine. She's just asleep.
Kariya-kun?
What? What's this all about?
What are you doing here?
Your face...
This is the Matou family magic.
You offer your flesh, and let it
eat away at your life.
And your sacrifice is repaid with magic.
But Sakura-chan's okay.
I promise to save her before
she ends up like me.
Zouken cares only for the Holy Grail.
He promised to free Sakura-chan
if I win it for him.
The Holy Grail?
Yes, so there's nothing to fear.
My Servant is the strongest.
No one stands a chance against him.
Right now, even clinging to hope
is painful for Sakura-chan.
So pray for her, in her stead.
Pray that I win,
that Sakura-chan has a future...
Kariya-kun, you...
Someday, we'll all come to this park
and play, like we used to.
And Rin-chan and Sakura-chan can
be sisters, like they once were.
So you don't have to cry
anymore, Aoi-san.
Kariya-kun... Do you want to die?
To take Tokiomi with you?
Mother?
Rin! I was so worried...
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry...
Kirei-sama,
shall I leave Tohsaka Tokiomi's
wife and daughter
to their own devices?
Yes. Continue to trail
Berserker's Master.
Understood.
It wasn't much, but I managed
to accomplish something.
Not that I'm ready to stand
on my own just yet.
After all, I passed out, right in
the middle of everything.
It just means I've still
got a lot to learn.
But that's only true for now.
I have plenty of time.
Someday, I'll have my turn to fight,
as a full Tohsaka mage.
That's why I'm working hard,
and following my father's teachings.
So that, no matter when that day comes,
I just have to give it everything I've got,
while maintaining a refined composure.
Episode 10
Rin's Adventure
A weak king is not even fit
to decorate the throne!
What good is a king who ignores
the plight of the weak?
We have nothing to lose.
A Reality Marble?
I shall have to kill you personally.
Don't you wanna conquer the world?
Next Time
Discussing the Grail