Now commencing the
57th Exterior Scouting Mission!
Move out!
After setting out to establish
a route to Shiganshina,
the Scout Regiment
encountered a female Titan
that was believed to be a
transformed human, similar to Eren.
It's not an Abnormal!
It's a human clad in a Titan body!
As soldier after soldier fell,
the regiment rushed
into a forest of giant trees,
much to everyone's puzzlement.
Who can possibly stop it,
if not the Levi Squad?!
Choose.
Will you trust yourself,
or me, these guys,
and the entire Scout Regiment?
I'll go with you!
Fire!
Oh, right.
There's one thing I need to ask.
Will you be fine if your limbs get cut off?
They'll go grow back, right?
I'm talking about your actual body.
Can't afford to have
you die on us, after all...
This goes to show that the enemy
was prepared to throw away everything.
I never imagined our target
would resort to Titan cannibalization
to dispose of information...
All soldiers, withdraw!
Redeploy the formation!
Return to Calaneth District!
Erwin.
Why did you have
Levi replenish his supplies
when there's no time to waste?
The female was eaten.
But did you see the
person inside get eaten?
I didn't.
Are you saying...?!
Yes.
If, as you deduced earlier,
we're dealing with a type that remains
able-bodied after de-transformation...
And, if said person had equipped
themselves with ODM gear in advance...
...that means they're now
wearing one of our uniforms...
Captain Levi?
No... It's not!
Who are you?!
Mr. Gunther!
...and have blended in
with the rest of us soldiers.
I won't let your deaths be meaningless
even if I'm the last one standing
In both hands, Gloria
What sings is Sieg
On my back, Flügel der Freiheit
Clenched determination to my left chest
What slashes across is Linie der Torheit
Soaring across the azure skies
Flügel der Freiheit
"Crushing Blow"
"The 57th Exterior Scouting Mission, Part 5"
When the Colossal Titan disappeared,
the person on the inside had
equipped ODM gear in advance,
which allowed for a quick
escape before the steam cleared.
The same thing could've happened here.
But didn't we conclude that
that was extremely unlikely,
based on Eren's condition
after emerging from his Titan?
His equipment was broken,
and even his combat uniform was gone.
Most of all, Eren was so fatigued
he couldn't even stand on his own.
The Female Titan had the ability
to attract Titans with her shrieking.
The operation failed because
we hadn't anticipated that.
If there are different levels
of mastery to this Titan ability,
we were mistaken to assume that Eren,
a novice, set the standard.
If we're to get the better of this enemy,
we'll need to think more resourcefully.
If we're withdrawing, does that
mean the operation was a success?
If so, they might've found out who
was inside the Female Titan by now.
I'd love to see their face.
Still, how was the commander so sure
that she'd come after
us once Eren left the wall?
I think it's because the
Titans suddenly stopped attacking
halfway through
their invasion a while back.
Huh?
They went to the trouble of
demolishing Trost District's front gate...
...but they didn't try
to destroy the inner gate,
nor did they take action
when Eren went to seal the hole.
My guess is that something
else suddenly came up.
Like what?
Something that took the
focus off of destroying the wall.
Something unexpected that happened...
Eren's transformation?!
I think that's the only possibility.
Which means...
Uhh, basically...
It was someone who was there...
Someone who had
actually seen Eren transform...
They're the Titan!
Mr. Gunther!
Eren! Don't stop!
Keep moving!
But Mr. Gunther is...!
--Who's that?!
--Protect Eren!
Damn! What now?! Which way do we go, Eld?!
There's no time to get our horses!
Head for HQ at full speed!
Is it the Female's operator?!
Or is there more than one?!
Damn! You'll pay for this!
You're going down,
even if I have to die too!
The Female Titan?!
You can't be serious... How?!
I thought we'd caught her?!
If the enemy can remain able-bodied...
...it's possible it can
make the Titan reappear, too.
I knew it!
It's coming!
The Female Titan!
Damn... How could you?!
This time I will kill her myself!
No!
The three of us will take her down!
You just keep heading
for HQ as fast as you can!
Faced with this opponent,
I've come to feel
that we have no hope
of surpassing the enemy
by sticking to the best course of action.
We need to take
serious risks when necessary
and be prepared to
lose everything in a fight.
I'll fight too!
No!
This is the best course of action!
We can't risk losing your ability!
What the hell, man?!
Do you doubt our skills or somethin'?!
Is that it, Eren?!
Do you really have
that little faith in us?!
Unless we fight that way...
...humanity can never win.
I have faith in our squad's victory!
Good luck!
We've blinded her!
She should be in complete
darkness for at least a minute!
--We'll finish you before then!
--The hell with capturing you!
--We're gonna kill you!
--Die a miserable death!
You're gonna pay, bitch!
Forget about getting your eyes back!
We're gonna shave
your shoulder muscles off
until you can't hold
your arms up anymore!
We're going to carve you up...
...and lop your arms...
...off!
They're down!
Next is the neck!
Once we sever the
muscles supporting the neck...
...we can go for the nape!
They're good!
They have her totally overwhelmed!
And they pulled off a coordinated
attack just like that, without a word!
It must be because they
trust each other as teammates.
That's how they've lasted so long.
That's why they're so tough
even right after losing Mr. Gunther!
I gotta keep moving!
I just gotta trust everyone and
keep moving without looking back!
That's the right choice!
I finally know the right answer!
I don't know the answer to that.
I never have.
Whether I trusted myself
or the choices of my dependable comrades,
there was no telling
how things would turn out.
Say goodbye to your nape!
Eld!
How?!
There's no way she can see yet!
It hasn't even been thirty seconds--
Only one eye?!
She healed just one eye quicker?!
She can do that?!
Petra! Pull yourself together!
Petra! Hurry!
That's it...
You're dead!
What? Why didn't my blades penetrate it?
I'm going to...
...kill her!
Eren?!
Hey! Wha...?! Mikasa!
That roar... Don't tell me it's...!
I made the wrong choice...
Choosing to trust my teammates...
...got them all killed!
If only I had trusted myself
and fought from the very start...!
If only I had killed
her from the very start...!
Back then...
If I had changed into a Titan...
No...
If I had fought even earlier than then...
Captain Levi was there too...
We would have beaten her.
We could've even captured her!
You're not in the wrong.
If you wanna do it, do it.
I made my...
I made my choice.
And that choice...
...got everyone killed.
It's my fault they're dead...
But... more than anything...
...it's all your fault!
I'm going to tear you apart...
Once my hands heal...
...I'm going to tear you apart...
piece by piece...
...into tiny little shreds...
...and then eat you!
A--
Eren!
W-Wait...
Eren...
Don't go...
Give Eren...
...back!
Give him back!
Why can't my blades penetrate it?!
He is alive!
Eren...
...is alive!
Wherever you are,
I'm going to slaughter this girl,
butcher her body,
and get you out of that foul place...
Sorry, Eren...
Just hang on a little longer...
Wait!
Wh-What...?!
Stay back for now.
Maintain this distance.
She's must be worn out, too.
She's not so fast anymore.
It looked like she bit the entire nape off.
Is Eren dead?
If, by chance, I'm not me
then who's to say that you're you?
Can you pick up the pieces of your heart
that fell apart like a broken sand castle?
The voice of someone calling out
changed into ringing in my ears
It's as if time has stopped
Now wake up
I made my way out of the deep darkness
I fled like a swift wind
We used to be like living corpses,
but now we head beyond the walls
Let's meet again
in a place not on any map
"Eren is alive."
"Give Eren back."
After helplessly watching
Eren get taken away,
Mikasa fights alongside Levi,
humanity's greatest soldier,
in a battle against the Female Titan.
"The Defeated"
"The 57th Exterior Scouting Mission, Part 6"