It's over!
Homura-chan...
You...
What the hell did you just do?!
I see. You're that anomaly, huh?
You're using a strange technique there.
Don't get in the way!
Sayaka-chan!
She's okay. She's just unconscious.
Who are you?
Whose side are you on?
I'm on the side of those who maintain their composure,
and I'm the enemy of the idiots who initiate fights needlessly.
Which are you, Sakura Kyouko?
Wha—
Have we met before?
I wonder.
I won't fight you since I haven't a single clue what hand you're gonna play.
I'll back down for today.
A prudent course of action.
You saved her?
How many times must I warn you?
Just how big of a fool are you?
I have warned you numerous times not to get involved, correct?
I...
I will not hold back against a fool.
Homura-chan... why?
At any rate, it's obvious she's planning something.
Be careful.
Akemi Homura, you can't be...
I will never forget the promise we made.
交わした約束忘れないよ
I'll close my eyes and make sure of that.
目を閉じ確かめる
I'll cast off this darkness that has descended upon me and move forward.
押し寄せた闇振り払って進むよ
When will I be able to see the future
いつになったらなくした未来を
that I had lost?
私ここでまた見ることできるの？
I'll walk upon this Earth,
あふれ出した不安の影を
cutting away these overflowing shadows of unease as many times as necessary.
何度でも裂いてこの世界歩んでこう
The clock that's endlessly ticked away now tells of the beginning.
とめどなく刻まれた時は今始まり告げ
Let's open the once-closed door,
変わらない思いを乗せ
carrying these unchanging feelings.
閉ざされた扉開けよう
My heart awoke and started racing to paint the future.
目覚めた心は走り出した 未来を描くため
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
難しい道で立ち止まっても空は
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me, so I won't be afraid.
きれいな青さでいつも待っててくれる	だから怖くない
No matter what happens, I won't give in.
もう何があってもくじけない
Episode 6  There's definitely something wrong with this
mwra
Miki
Now you should be fine for a while.
Wow, it turned black.
It's dangerous now. If you taint it any further, a witch might hatch.
It's fine. Give it to me.
Now it'll be fine.
You ate it?!
It's one aspect of my job.
But in order to continue purifying your Soul Gem, you'll need to find a new Grief Seed.
Is it really that important to keep this bright?
Sakura Kyouko was strong, right?
If you have a Soul Gem that's got plenty of room to spare, you can use all the magic you want without concern.
That's the source of Kyouko's power.
But that doesn't mean you can just sacrifice innocent people to get Grief Seeds.
The more you use magic, the more it taints your Soul Gem.
Sayaka, you should assume you can't beat Kyouko until you acquire some Grief Seeds.
This is kinda...
Mami-san didn't have enough Grief Seeds, right?
But she was able to fight just fine.
Are some magical girls just more talented?
Well, that's definitely true.
That sucks!
That's not fair at all!
You can't really help that.
Not only does Kyouko have talent, she's also a veteran.
But there are completely inexperienced geniuses who could surpass magical girls like Kyouko through pure talent.
Who would that be?
Kaname Madoka.
Madoka?
Is that true?
Yeah.
That's why if you really want an edge in your fight with Kyouko, you could always ask her.
If she contracts with me...
No!
This is my fight.
I can't get her involved.
A note to customers
Please do not play and eat or drink at the same time.
We reserve the right to refuse customers attempting to hit on customers, perform sales, or
otherwise attempt to take customers to other locales.
Hey. What do you want this time?
I want to leave this city to you.
What brought this about?
Girls like you are fit to be magical girls.
Miki Sayaka is incompatible.
Hmph, that was always the plan.
What are you planning to do about this Sayaka girl? If you just leave her be, she's going to charge back in again.
I want to end this as peacefully as possible.
Don't interfere. I'll take care of it.
You still haven't told me what I need to know.
Who are you?
What are you after?
A Walpurgis Night will come to this town two weeks from today.
How do you know that?
That's a secret.
Anyway, once that's defeated, I'll leave this city.
You can do what you want after that.
A Walpurgis Night, huh?
That'd be pretty hard to handle myself, but we might be able to win if we team up.
Want some?
It's not going to work. Too much time has passed.
It doesn't look like we have any clues to help locate the familiar from last night.
I see...
Hey, Sayaka-chan.
If you continue to hunt witches, won't you run into the girl from yesterday again?
Well, I guess I would have to, yeah.
Then you should go find her and try to talk things over.
If you don't, you'll end up fighting again before you know it.
A fight, huh?
Did last night look like a normal fight to you?
That wasn't just a fight—we were trying to kill each other.
We were only messing around in the beginning.
By the time we were halfway through, we were seriously trying to kill each other.
That... makes it even worse.
And you want me to try to talk to her?!
Don't be stupid.
She's someone who wants to treat humans like live bait just to get more Grief Seeds.
How am I supposed to get along with someone like that?
Sayaka-chan, you became a magical girl to fight witches, right?
That girl isn't a witch... she's a magical girl like you!
There's a way to get along if you look for it.
Even if she does things differently, you both want to take out witches, right? I'm sure she feels the same.
Homura-chan too.
If Mami-san didn't fight with Homura-chan...
That wouldn't have happened!
You saw her, didn't you?
She waited for Mami-san to get killed before she came to kill the witch!
She let Mami-san die because she wanted the Grief Seed!
That's not what happened...
That transfer student is the same as Kyouko!
They only think about themselves!
I understand that now.
Mami-san was the only one who was different.
All the other magical girls are like those two!
No...
The familiar that got away last night was a small fry, but it'll still kill people!
It could go after your mom or dad next!
Maybe even Takkun!
And you're saying you don't care about that?
Could you really forgive someone if they just let that happen?
I'm not just fighting against witches.
I wanted this power to fight to protect people I care about.
That's why I'll fight anyone worse than the witches themselves.
Even if that person is another magical girl.
Sayaka-chan...
Kyubey, say something to her...
The only thing I can tell her is that she's being too reckless.
Sayaka currently has no chance of winning against Akemi Homura or Sakura Kyouko.
But she won't listen to what I say.
Settings
Menu
Time
Settings
Timer
Recall
Preset
Heat
Water
Fill With
Hot Water
Heat
Water
Fill With
Hot Water
Heat
Water
Fill With
Hot Water
Time
Settings
Timer
Heat
Water
Time
Settings
Timer
Heat
Water
Time
Settings
Timer
Fill With
Hot Water
Time
Settings
Timer
Welcome Home
There's some potato salad in the fridge
Tomo
Can't sleep?
Yeah... mind if I sit down?
Things are going really poorly with my friend.
What she's doing and saying probably isn't wrong, but the more she tries to do what's right, the worse everything gets.
That happens a lot.
It sucks, but you can't reach a happy ending just by doing what's right all the time.
Actually, the more people get stubborn and insist that they're in the right, the farther away happiness gets.
It's terrible not being able to be happy even though you're not wrong.
Yeah.
What should I do...
Well, even if someone said something, it wouldn't work itself out nicely, huh?
Do you want to solve this, even if what you choose to do isn't the prettiest method?
Yeah.
Then you just have to do something wrong.
Huh?
Somebody has to be in the wrong to balance out her need to be in the right.
Do something wrong?
Tell a white lie, or run away from something scary.
Sometimes you realize that was actually the best choice in the end.
Sometimes when you hit a dead end with no real alternatives, making a big mistake is an option.
Would they understand that I was doing it for them?
They might not. Especially right afterwards.
I told you it might not be the nicest way to do it.
But which do you think is better: you giving up on her completely, or her getting the wrong idea about you?
Madoka, you grew up to be a good girl.
You don't lie, and you don't do anything bad.
You're always trying hard to do what is right.
You're already a wonderful child.
That's why you should start studying how to make mistakes before you grow up.
Studying?
When you're young, you recover from getting hurt faster.
If you learn how to fall down now, it'll be easier for you later on.
When you get older, making mistakes gets harder.
The more things you're responsible for, the less mistakes you can make.
I see.
Isn't that hard?
Being an adult is hard for everybody.
That's why they let you drink.
I want to grow up and drink with you.
Hurry up and get older. As difficult as it is, it's fun being an adult.
Oh, Kamijou-san was released from the hospital yesterday.
His rehabilitation was going well, so his schedule was moved up.
I-I see...
Kami
You're going to go home without even seeing him?
You chased after him all day, too.
You're...
I already know. The boy in this house, right?
He's the reason why you made a contract with Kyubey.
My god, you used your only chance for a miracle on something retarded.
What do you know about what happened?!
You're the one who doesn't get it, idiot.
Magic is supposed to be used one hundred percent for granting your own wishes.
No good comes out of using it for someone else.
Tomoe Mami didn't teach you about that either?
Kami
If you want to make a guy you fell in love with yours, there's a better option using the magic you just got.
Wh-What?
Rush in there right now and break his hands and legs so he'll never be able to use them again.
Make it so he won't be able to do anything without you anymore.
Then he'll be yours. His heart, body, everything.
Kami
If you'd feel bad about that, I can always do it for you.
You know, common courtesy between magical girls.
It'd be simple.
I'll never... I'll never forgive you.
This time I'll...
How about we go somewhere else?
People'll probably see us here.
Somebody has to be in the wrong to balance out her need to be in the right.
Yeah, but...
Madoka!
Hurry! Sayaka's in trouble!
Follow me!
We won't need to hold back here.
Let's go all out.
Wait Sayaka-chan!
Ma-Madoka!
Don't get in the way.
This isn't even any of your business.
No, there's definitely something weird about this!
Hmph. It's not surprising that the annoying bitch has an annoying friend.
Then what would that make your friend?
Damn.
This isn't what we discussed.
I thought I told you to keep your hands off of Miki Sayaka.
Your method wouldn't get the message across!
She's not backing down either way.
I'll take her on then. Don't get involved.
Then I'll wait until I'm done eating this.
That's plenty of time.
I won't be that easy!
Sayaka-chan, I'm sorry!
Madoka, what the hell?!
But if I didn't...
Sayaka-chan?
That was bad, Madoka.
There must be something wrong with you, throwing your friend like that.
What... What are you saying?
Stop it!
What's going on?!
She's dead!
Sayaka-chan?
Hey, Sayaka-chan?
Wake up! Say something! Wh-What's wrong?
I don't want this to happen!
Sayaka-chan!
What the hell is going on?
Hey!
You magical girls can only control your bodies from 100 meters away, at most.
100 meters?!
What? What the hell does that mean?
You normally walk around with them, so accidents like this rarely happen.
What are you saying, Kyubey?
Save her! Don't let Sayaka-chan die!
Madoka... That's not Sayaka. It's just an empty container.
You just threw Sayaka.
Wh-What...?
I couldn't ask you to fight witches with a fragile body just like a normal person's.
A magical girl's old body is nothing more than a piece of external hardware.
Your actual soul is given a much safer, compact form that is capable of controlling magic much more efficiently.
It's part of my job, when I complete a magical girl contract.
I remove your souls and change them into Soul Gems.
What the hell did you do to us?
You bastard! You basically turned us into zombies!
Isn't it more convenient that way?
Even if your heart is torn to shreds, or you lose every drop of blood in your body,
if you heal that damage with magic, you'll be able to operate again right away.
You're basically invincible, provided that your Soul Gem doesn't break.
Isn't that much more useful during a fight than a human body full of potential problems?
That's terrible... That's really awful.
You're all the same. You always act the same way when you're told what's going on.
I don't get it.
Why do humans place so much value on where their soul is located?
What?
What's wrong?
Someday the light of love you hold within your eyes will transcend time
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光がときを超えて
and destroy the dream of a world racing towards destruction.
滅び急ぐ世界の夢を確かに一つ壊すだろう
Now that you've drank every ounce of your hesitation, what do you desire?
躊躇いを飲み干して君が望むものは何？
Will there be a fleeting tomorrow for this greedy admiration?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に儚い明日はあるの？
I want to see you, smiling with the power to shatter even darkness,
子供の頃夢に見てた古の魔法のように
like the ancient magic I saw in my dreams when I was young.
闇さえ砕く力で微笑む君に会いたい
Everything depends on these feelings of courage from the flower that was plucked
怯えるこの手の中には手折られた花の勇気
that now lays in my frightened hands.
思いだけが頼るすべて
This wish will awaken that light.
光を呼び覚ます願い
Illustrator Ueda Hajime
You had a wish so important that you agreed to a fate of combat, am I correct?
And your wish came true, didn't it?
Can you come to terms with how you really feel?
Episode 7   Can you come to terms with how you really feel?
Translator: Miku
Translation Check (Native JP/JP ONLY): Aya & Chika
Editor: limitbreakingcat
Timer: euronymous
Typesetter: thedarkhaze
Quality Check: kozu
rune
thedarkhaze
King_Arthur
Robo210